

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER SILATSA IVAN



📞 +237 681832508 🔛 ivansilatsa@gmail.com 🌐 https://github.com/ivan01-tech

About Me

I'm a student at the University of Douala, I'm 21 years old. I'm a full-stack web developer, and I use React.JS and NextJS to build frontend applications and Node (Express and NestJS) to build backend applications. My main aim is to build, test, and deploy web apps using JavaScript technologies.

Contact Me

https://twitter.com/ivansilatsa



https://github.com/ivan01-tech



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ ivan-silatsa-581152264/

Skills

HTML	
css	
Javascript	
Typescript	
React.JS(NextJS)	
NestJS	
NodeJS(Express)	
Sql/Mysql	
Neo4j	
MongoDB	

Languages

French	
Enalish	

Educational

2018-2019 **Makepe High School**

It's where i got my bachelor's degree

2021 - present University of Douala in Cameroon

> I study computer science in the university of Douala since 2021 and i'm in level 2 now.

Experiences

2021 - present

Learning period

I start with the frontend development in 2021 with HTML, CSS and Javascript. Then i continue by learning ReactJS and Nodejs/ ExpressJs frameworks. I realized some small projects during my learning period.

2022

Realization of a note-taking app

In the month of November 2022, i built an application that can help people store their notes, modify them, and delete them. They can also search them by tags. I used ReactJS and Typescript to build it. Link over here: https://note-taking-app-phi.vercel.app/

Realization of a chat application

During the last week of 2022, I started building an application where someone can send messages and images to a group of people in a specific room in real time. Users register by entering their nickname and the name of the room they want to join.

The link: https://chat-app-cucz.onrender.com/

2023

Invoice Generator

From February 2023 to May 2023, I built an application to generate invoices and send them to someone by email. It took me around 3 months to build this, and I was learning enough while doing this project. I use ReactJS, NodeJS (Express), and Nodemailer to do that.

Link to the project: https://github.com/ivan01-tech/invoicegenerator

Nested comments system

I also built a blog with an advanced system of comments where people can add new comments related to a specific post, update their comments, delete them, and also reply to other comments in an infinite way. It's like a small Reddit clone. I did it by using ReactJS, Node (Express), Prisma, and Tailwind CSS. The link is: https://github.com/ivan01-tech/nested-comments-system